Finding Aid for the The Donald Grady Davidson Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- APPENDIX B-- LITERARY CAREER-LIST OF CLIPPINGS ABOUT DAVIDSON'S WORK, 1924 - 1968
  - New York Times: "From Civil War to TVA," review of The Tennessee, Vol. II, By Horace Reynolds., Jan. 26, 1948
  - Sun (N. Y., N. Y.): " A River's Stirring History in the Civil War and Later," Review by Clayton Hoagland., Jan. 26, 1948
  - Globe (Boston, Mass.): "The Tennessee.", Jan. 29, 1948
  - Army Times (Washington, D. C.): citation of The Tennessee, Vol. II., Jan. 31, 1948
  - Science News Letter (Washington, D. C.): citation of The Tennessee, Vol. II., Jan. 31, 1948
  - Journal American (N. Y., N. Y.): review of The Tennessee., Jan. 31, 1948
  - Saturday Review of Literature (N. Y, N. Y.): "Liquid Mason-Dixon Line," Review of The Tennessee, The New River:... by Willson Whitman., Jan. 31, 1948
  - Book of the Month Club News (N.Y., N. Y.): "How the Tennessee Has Influenced History.", Feb. 1948
  - Booklist: review of The Tennessee, Vol. II., Feb. 1, 1948
  - World (Tulsa, Oklahoma): review of The Tennessee, Vol. II., Feb. 1, 1948
  - Journal (Milwaukee, WI): " The Tennessee: River of Strife and Kilowatts," Reviewed by Harry Pease., Feb. 1, 1948
  - Commercial Appeal (Memphis, TN): "The Tennessee: New River Traces Streams History From War of 1860's/Davidson's Vol II Lacks Rugged Drama of First Part," Review by P.F., Feb. 1, 1948
  - Star (Washington, D. C.): "In the TVA Valley," review of The Tennessee, Vol.II, By James Birchfield., Feb. 8, 1948
  - Chicago Tribune: "Tennessee River Volume Develops Its Late History," Reviewed by August Derleth., Feb. 8, 1948
  - Mail (Anderson, S.C.): review of The Tennessee, Vol. II., Feb. 11, 1948
  - Record (Columbia, S. C.): "A Turbulent River/ The Story of the Tennessee And Momentous Events Nearby," review by Alderman Duncan., Feb. 12, 1948
  - Enquirer (Cincinnati, Ohio): "Walter Winchell," (column)., Feb. 12, 1948
  - Star (Kansas City, MO.): "Tennessee River Story," review by W.W.B., Feb. 14, 1948
  - Patriot Ledger (Quincy, Mass.): review of The Tennessee, Vol. II., Feb. 14, 1948
  - St. Louis Post Dispatch: " An Ingrown Southerner Looks at TVA,' review By Rufus Terral., Feb. 15, 1948
  - Spokesman Review (Spokane, Washington): "Rivers of America", Feb. 15, 1948
  - Republican (Pottsville, PA): review of The Tennessee, Vol. II., Feb. 20, 1948
  - Advertiser (Tiffin, Ohio): citation of The Tennessee, Vol. II., Feb. 21, 1948
  - Intermountain (Elkins, W. Va.): citation of The Tennessee, Vol. II., Feb. 21, 1948
  - Observer and Budget (Troy, N. Y.): citation of The Tennessee, Vol. II., Feb. 22, 1948
  - News (Jackson, Miss.): "New Volume in River Series on Tennessee.", Feb. 22, 1948
  - Citizen (Asheville, N. C.): citation of The Tennessee, Vol. II., Feb. 22, 1948
  - Mail (Hagerstown, Md.): citation of The Tennessee, Vol. II., Feb. 24, 1948
  - Item (Portchester, N. Y.): citation of The Tennessee, Vol. II., Feb. 24, 1948
  - News (Beloit, Wisc.): citation of The Tennessee, Vol. II., Feb. 26, 1948
  - Journal (Pottsville, PA): citation of The Tennessee, Vol. II., Feb. 26, 1948
  - Herald Enterprises (Bellflower, Cal.): citation of The Tennessee, Vol. II., Feb. 27, 1948
  - Nashville Banner: "South's Frontier Life," review of Everett Dick's The Dixie Frontier, By Mortimer Truil., Feb. 27, 1948
  - Post (Vicksburg, Miss.): "Vicksburesque", Feb. 27, 1948
  - Independent (Richmond, Cal.): citation of The Tennessee, Vol. II., Feb. 28, 1948
  - Press Herald (Portland, Maine): " The Tennessee.", Feb. 29, 1948
  - News (Dallas, Texas): " Of Tennessee River and TVA," review by John H. Mcginnis., Feb. 29, 1948
  - Folder
  - Book Review Digest (N.Y., N. Y.): citation of The Tennessee, Vol. II., March, 1948
  - The Southern Packet (Asheville, N. C.): "The Perennial Problem: The Club Program," by Agatha Boyd Adams., March 1948
  - Press-Gazette (Green Bay, Wis.): "Son of the Valley Writes History of Tennessee River.", March 1, 1948
  - Record (Meriden, Conn.): "Have you Read/ The Tennessee/ The Everglades", March 2, 1948
  - Evening News (San Jose, Cal.): "The Tennessee-Civil War to TVA.", March 2, 1948
  - News (San Francisco, Cal.): "The Tennessee-Civil War to TVA.", March 2, 1948
  - Gazette (Taunton, Mass.): "The Tennessee-Civil War to TVA.", March 6, 1948
  - Press (Atlantic City, N. J.): "The Tennessee-Civil War to TVA.", March 7, 1948
  - Times (Wichita Falls, Texas): "The Tennessee-Civil War to TVA.", March 7, 1948
  - News (North Kansas City, Mo.): "A New King is Crowned.", March 8, 1948
  - News Tribune (Fullerton, Cal.): citation of The Tennessee, Vol. II., March 9, 1948
  - Eagle (Butler, Pa.): citation of The Tennessee, Vol. II., March 11, 1948
  - Herald-Times (Manitowoc, Wisconsin): "The Tennessee... Donald Davidson.", March 12, 1948
  - Gazette (Gastonia, N. C.): "Book Reviews," of The Tennessee, Vol.II, By Ben and Estelle Atkins., March 13, 1948
  - Register (Torrington, Conn.): citation of The Tennessee, Vol. II., March 15, 1948
  - Messenger (St. Albans, Vt.): citation of The Tennessee, Vol. II., March 16, 1948
  - Piedmont (Greenville, S. C.): citation of The Tennessee, Vol. II., March 18, 1948
  - Journal (Lewiston, Maine): citation of The Tennessee, Vol. II., March 18, 1948
  - Press-Telegram (Long Beach, Cal.): "Literary Works Lead Current Affairs Books.", March 20, 1948
  - Times Herald (Dallas, Texas): "Many Lakes and a River." By William H. Vann., March 21, 1948
  - Observer (Charlotte, N. C.): citation of The Tennessee, Vol. II., March 21, 1948
  - Journal (Meriden, Conn.): citation of The Tennessee, Vol.II., March 24, 1948
  - Friends of American Writers News (Chicago, Illinois): citation of The Tennessee, Vol. II.., April, 1948
  - Southern Packet (Asheville, N. C.): "The Tennessee: Modern." Review by Paul M. Fink., April 1948
  - Holiday: "The Tennessee: The New River-Civil War to TVA.", April 1948
  - Gate City (Keokuki, Iowa): citation of The Tennessee, Vol. II., April 1, 1948
  - Telegram (Superior, Wisconsin): citation of The Tennessee, Vol. II., April 2, 1948
  - Times (Kingsport, Tn.): "This Week's Best Sellers in Kingsport.", April 4, 1948
  - Observer (Dunkirk, N. Y.): citation of The Tennessee, Vol II., April 5, 1948
  - Journal (Antigo, Wisconsin): citation of The Tennessee, Vol. II., April 8, 1948
  - Sentinel Mist (St. Helens, Oregon): citation of The Tennessee, Vol. II., April 9, 1948
  - Intelligencer-Journal (Lancaster, Pa.): "Southern River.", April 10, 1948
  - Nashville Banner: "Donald Davidson Receives Honorary Degree From W & L.", April 12, 1948
  - Nashville Tennessean: " Donald Davidson Given Honorary W & L Degree.", April 13, 1948
  - Nation (N. Y., N. Y.): " The Giant-TVA," review of David Lilienthal, Public Servant in a Power Age, by Willson Whitman, and of The Tennessee, Vol. II, By Ernest Kirschten., April 17, 1948
  - Sun & Times (Chicago, Ill.): "How the TVA Gave River A ‘New Look,'" By C. Herman Pritchett., April 18, 1948
  - Herald (Albany, Ga.): citation of The Tennessee, Vol. II., April 18, 1948
  - Folder
  - Record Herald (Richmond, Cal.): citation of The Tennessee, Vol. II., April 21, 1948
  - Reporter (Two Rivers, Wisconsin: citation of The Tennessee, Vol II., April 22, 1948
  - Patriot Ledger (Quincy, Mass.): citation of The Tennessee, Vol. II., April 23, 1948
  - Gazette (Xenia, Ohio): citation of The Tennessee, Vol. II., April 29, 1948
  - Picayune (New Orleans, La.): "River of Destiny.", May 2, 1948
  - Senior Scholastic (N. Y., N. Y.): citation of The Tennessee, Vol. II., May 3, 1948
  - America (N. Y,, N. Y.): citation of The Tennessee, Vol. II., May 8, 1948
  - Gazette (Little Rock, Arkansas): "Down South.", May 9, 1948
  - Post (Boston, Mass.): citation of The Tennessee, Vol. II., May 9, 1948
  - Christian Science Monitor (Boston, Mass.): "Tennessee Valley: 3 Periods," The Tennessee, Vol. II., reviewed by R.M. H., May 15, 1948
  - Chronicle (Augusta, Ga.): citation of The Tennessee, Vol. II., May 16, 1948
  - Journal (Providence, R. I.): " The Tennessee-Civil War to TVA," review By K. B. R., May 16, 1948
  - Current History: review of The Tennessee, Vol. II., July 1948
  - Union (Fort Atkinson, Wis.): citation of The Tennessee, Vol. II, July 8, 1948
  - Daily (Decatur, Ala.): "Books/The Tennessee/ By Donald Davidson.", July 11, 1948
  - Courant (Hartford, Conn.): "River Victor in Two Wars," The Tennessee, Vol. II, reviewed by Maxine Tull Boatner., Aug. 22, 1948
  - Southern Packet (Asheville, N. C.): "Poetry.", Sept., 1948
  - Townsman (Andover, Mass.): citation of The Tennessee, Vol. II., Sept. 16, 1948
  - Southern Packet (Asheville, N. C.): citation of The Tennessee, Vol. II., Dec. 1948
  - Education: review of The Tennessee, Vol.II, by William P. Sears., Feb. 1949
  - Peabody Bi-Monthly: citation of The Tennessee, Vol. II., March 1949
  - N. Y. Times: " A Tribute to the Persistence of Poets," review of Lee In the Mountains, and The Wind of Time by Rolfe Humphries, review by Phyllis McGinley., July 31, 1949
  - Nashville Tennessean Magazine: "He Clings to Enduring Values," by Louise Davis., Sept. 4, 1949
  - New York Times, citation of Lee in the Mountains., Dec. 4, 1949
  - Folder
  - Commercial Appeal (Memphis, Tn.): "Davidson on Yeats.", Feb. 5, 1950
  - Record (Columbia, S. C.): "Southern Literary Leader Visits in Columbia," by Louis Jones DuBose., Dec. 14, 1950
  - Nashville Tennessean: no title; report on Davidson's activities., Jan. 21, 1951
  - News(Charleston, S. C.): "Books and People.", Jan. 28, 1951
  - News (Charleston, S.C.): ":The Letters of William Gilmore Simms.", March 2, 1954
  - Peabody Journal of Education (Nashville, Tn.): citation of American Composition and Rhetoric., Jan., 1954
  - Nashville Tennessean: "Twenty Lessons in Reading and Writing Prose.", May 15, 1955
  - Nashville Banner: "Literary Leaders to Meet at V. U. for 3 Day Parley Of Fugitive Poets., May 1, 1956
  - The Evening Sun (Baltimore, MD.): "Books in Review/ Essays in Literature," Review of Still Rebels, Still Yankees and Other Essays, by Louis D. Rubin, Jr., March 21, 1957
  - Library Journal (N. Y., N. Y.): review of Still Rebels, Still Yankees and Other Essays., April 1, 1957
  - Commercial Appeal (Memphis, Tn): " U. S. Conscience Commands Look By Two Writers," by Paul Flowers., April 7, 1957
  - Tribune (Chicago, Ill.): "Among the Authors," by Frederic Babcock., April 7, 1957
  - Nashville Tennessean: citation of The Attack on Leviathan., April 14, 1957
  - Nashville Tennessean: " V. U. Prof Explores Basic Human Issues.", April 14, 1957
  - Book List (Chicago, Ill.): citation of, Still Yankees Still Rebels and Other Essays., April 15, 1957
  - Magazine of Books, Chicago Tribune: "Voice of the Reader/ The Hinterland.", April 21, 1957
  - Nashville Banner: "Rich Varied Commentary On Our Times," review Of Still Rebels, Still Yankees and Other Essays, by Brainard Cheney., April 26, 1957
  - Journal (Providence, R. I.): "Essays on the South," Still Rebels, Still Yankees, and Other Essays, reviewed by Charles H. Watts, II., April 28, 1957
  - Pilot (Norfolk, Va.): "Nostalgic Essays/Daydreams in Dixie," review Of Still Rebels, Still Yankees, and Other Essays by Frank Blackford., April 28, 1957
  - Tribune (Chicago, Ill.): "Many Stimulating Variations on a Single Theme," Review of Still Rebels, Still Yankees and Other Essays by Ben Ray Redman., April 28, 1957
  - Folder
  - Saturday Review: "Change vs. Tradition," Still Rebels, Still Yankees and Other Essays reviewed by J. T. W., May 4, 1957
  - America: no title; citation of Still Rebels, Still Yankees, and Other Essays, May 11, 1957
  - Times Dispatch (Richmond, Va.): review of Still Rebels, Still Yankees and Other Essays by Clifford Dowdey., June 2, 1957
  - Observer (Raleigh, N. C.): "Still Rebels.", June 9, 1957
  - Sun (Jackson, Tn.): "Teahouse of Southern Moon May Still Fit Together," Review of Still Rebels, Still Yankees, and Other Essays, by Prof. William B. Hesseltine., July 7, 1957
  - Oklahoman (Oklahoma City, Oklahoma): "Too Heavy, Too Zoned," Review of Kees, by J. P. Pritchard., July 7, 1957
  - Times (Chattanooga, Tn.): "But How Shall the South Act," review of Still Rebels, Still Yankees and Other Essays by Wilma Dykeman Stokely., July 20, 1957
  - America: review of Still Rebels, Still Yankees by Margaret Kenny., Aug. 3, 1957
  - South Atlantic Quarterly: review of Still Rebels, Still Yankees by Jay B. Hubbell., Autumn 1957
  - Annals of the American Academy of Political and Social Science: review of Still Rebels, Still Yankees by Ella Lonn., Sept. 1957
  - America: citation of Still Rebels, Still Yankees., Nov. 30, 1957
  - Sentinel (Grand Jct., Colo.): "Don Miller Memorial Collection.", Jan. 5, 1958
  - The Daily Reveille (L.S.U., Baton Rouge, La.): "Fugitive Group Discussed by Poet," by Angela Maspero., March 13, 1958
  - Commercial Appeal (Memphis, Tn.): "Fugitives Again.", June 1, 1958
  - Picayune (New Orleans, La.): citation of Southern Writers in the Modern World., June 15, 1958
  - Saturday Review (N. Y., N. Y.): citation of Southern Writers in the Modern World., June 21, 1958
  - Observer (Raleigh, N. C.): "Southern Accent.", June 29, 1958
  - Times (Chattanooga, Tn.): "Books and Writers," by Gilbert E. Govan., July 6, 1958
  - Va. Quarterly Review: review of Southern Writers in the Modern World., Autumn, 1958
  - Nashville Banner, "Recollections of Fugitives and Agrarians," review of Southern Writers in the Modern World, by Frances Neel Cheney., Sept. 7, 1958
  - Folder
  - ______,(Selma, Ala.): "Sensing the News," by Thurman Sensing., Sept. 18, 1960
  - Americus Times-Recorder (Americus, Ga.): "The Actual South" (editorial)., Sept. 19, 1960
  - Commercial Appeal (Memphis, Tn.): "Regional Actors Active," by Paul Flowers, Sept. 19, 1961
  - Anniston Star (Anniston, Ala.): "New Poems Published," The Long Street reviewed by Barbara Hodge Hall., Oct. 15, 1961
  - The Roanoke Times (Roanoke, Va.): "Books of the Times/Donald Davidson and His Poetry," by Paxton Davis., Oct. 15, 1961
  - Nashville Banner: "Creates Poetry That is Truly Universal," The Long Street reviewed by Robert L. Welker., Oct. 20, 1961
  - Nashville Tennessean, "Collected Poems Have Warmth, Distinction," The Long Street reviewed by Dean Kenneth England., Oct. 22, 1961
  - Southern Observer: "An Authentic Southern Voice," by Durant Da Ponte., Nov., 1961
  - News and Courier (Charleston, S. C.): "Davidson's Poetry," by John R. Doyle., Nov. 19, 1961
  - Richmond News Leader: "Major ‘Fugitive': Donald Davidson's Poetry Reveals Love of Tradition," The Long Street reviewed by Harry M. Meacham., Dec. 6, 1961
  - The Christian Century: " A Vatic Poet," The Long Street reviewed by Robert Drake., Dec. 27, 1961
  - Tulsa World (Tulsa, Okla.): citation of The Long Street by Bob Wyatt, Dec. 13, 1961
  - South Carolina Librarian (Vol. 6, No. 2): "Book Reviews," a review of The Long Street., _____, 1962
  - N. Y. Times Book Review:" Davidson's Long Street is the South.", Dec. 24, 1961
  - The Times Picayune (New Orleans, La.): "Collected Verse of a Fugitive," The Long Street reviewed by James W. Nolan., Jan. 21, 1962
  - The Evening Sun (Baltimore, Md.): "New Books in Review/Three Poets," The Long Street reviewed by Josephine Jcobsen., Jan. 22, 1962
  - Chattanooga Times: "Of Books and Writers," by Gilbert E. Govan, a review Of The Long Street., Jan. 28, 1962
  - Sunday Advocate (Baton Rouge, La.): "Donald Davidson's Poetry is Confident, Erudite, Honest," review of The Long Street by Miller Williams., Feb. 25, 1962
  - Nashville Banner: "Donald Davidson Honored by VU English Department.", _____,1965
  - Atlanta Journal: "Fugitive is Dead/Compare Agrarians, Black Power," by Roy Blount, Jr., _____, 1968
  - Atlanta Journal:" Attack Him Myself/ Davidson: Whole in His Acts," by Roy Blount, Jr., _____, 1968
  - Folder
  - Undated Newspaper Clippings About Davidson Arranged by Title:
  - "Authors to Lecture at Bread Loaf School/Noted Educators and Critics Also Named to Staff of Middlebury Summer Session." No newspaper title or place of publication.
  - "The Blooming Lyre," a review of An Outland Piper et al. By Arthur Guiterman; Outlook, April Book Supplement.
  - "Davidson Speaks on Poetry at U. C./Vanderbilt Professor Also Reads from Own Works in University Lecture," by Thomas Brahan. No newspaper title, Chattanooga, Tn.
  - "Davidson Talks on ‘Place of Poetry'/ Poet Can Be Interpreter in Time of Confusion, He Tells Civitans." No newspaper title or place of publication.
  - "Davidson To Talk To Knox Historians." No newspaper title or place of publication.
  - "Dixie Problems Agrarian. Industrialism Drawa Strong Attack by Vanderbilt Educator," by Walter Paschall. No newspaper title or place of publication given.
  - "Dr. Donald Davidson's Lecture." No newspaper title or place of publication given.
  - "Donald Davidson Appears In Lecture at Centennial Club." No newspaper title or place of publication given.
  - "Donald Davidson Discussed Modern Poetry Before Literary Department/Lecture Inaugurated Series of Studies for Centennial Club Members." Nashville Tennessean.
  - "Donald Davidson's Talk on Poetry Centennial Club Attraction." No newspaper title or place of publication given.
  - "A Far Fair Strain," An Outland Piper, reviewed by Joseph T. Shipley. No newspaper title or place of publication given.
  - "Future Poem Prizes Awarded." No newspaper title or place of publication given.
  - "Good Evenin'/What Did Lee Think of Surrender." No newspaper title or place of publication given.
  - "The Lantern," edited by J. C. Comfort. No newspaper title or place of publication given.
  - "The Literary Lantern," three different columns. No newspaper titles or places of publication given.
  - "Lucid, Yet Modern," Lee in the Mountains and OtherPoems reviewed by Richmond Croom Beatty. Nashville Banner or Nashville Tennessean.
  - "A Nashville ‘Fugitive' Talks for Robert E. Lee/Donald Davidson Shows Southern Poets Are Still Not Reconciled," by John Holmes. No newspaper title or place of publication Given.
  - "A Note on ‘The Fugitive'." The Vanderbilt Hustler.
  - "Our Book for the Week/ The Tall Men." The Cadet (Virginia Military Institute).
  - " An Outland Piper." No newspaper title or place of publication given.
  - "The Poet as Southerner," The Tall Men reviewed by Jay B. Hubbell. The Archive.
  - "Poetry Society of Tennessee Organized Saturday Evening." Nashville Banner.
  - "Roaming Tennessee Writers," by Gilbert E. Govan. No newspaper title or place of publication given.
  - "The Tall Men." The New Republic.
  - "Taste for Poetry Inherent in U. S./Donald Davidson Speaks at Luncheon Meeting of Kiwanis Club." Nashville Banner
  - "A Tennessee Poet," a review of The Tall Men by Willis Posey. Asheville Times (N.C.).
  - "Tennessee Story Told in American Rivers Chronicles," by George Barmann. Plain Dealer.
  - "'Undamaged Souls' Is Topic of Donald Davidson's Club Lecture." Nashville Banner or Nashville Tennessean.
  - "Verse That Entertains But Is Unimportant," comment on An Outland Piper and on Archibald MacLeish's The Happy Marriage. Untitled-two reviews of An Outland Piper One unrelated fragment Notice of Davidson's speaking before the American Association of University Women, No newspaper title or place of publication given.
  - "Industrialism Holds No Salvation For the South, Agrarian Warns," no newspaper title or place of publication given.
- Donald Davidson Papers
- Appendix C-Fugitives and Agrarians-List of Newspaper Clippings, 1924 -1936
  - Folder
  - [1924] The Nashville Tennessean:" By Far the Best of Its Kind in the South" a writer describing Davidson's Book and Literary Page in The Tennessean.
  - The Chicago Tribune: "More Poetry Prizes." Noting The Fugitive., April 5, 1924
  - New York Sun: "The Bear Garden Program-and Young Writers", January 16, ____
  - The Virginia Pilot and the Norfolk _____:" The Literary Lantern"-News of the Fugitives, May 21, 1926
  - Chattanooga News: "The Young Confederates.", Sept. 3, 1930
  - Macon Telegraph: "Lee, We Are Here!", Sept. 24, 1930
  - Washington Post: Review of I'll Take My Stand., Nov. 1, 1930
  - Virginian Pilot (Norfolk, Va.): "Our Own Kulturkampf", Nov. 10, 1930
  - Nashville Tennessean: "Book of Protest by 12 Southerners of Agrarian Tradition Issued Today.", Nov. 12, 1930
  - New York Morning World:The First Reader, "Voices of the South: Paris Gets Conservative," by Harry Hansen., Nov. 12, 1930
  - Nashville Banner: " I'll Take My Stand Is On Sale Today/Agrarianism Versus Industrialism Treated by Vanderbilt Writers.", Nov. 12, 1930
  - Leaf Chronicle (Clarksville, Tn.): "Local Authors To Hear A Debate at Richmond Virginia.", Nov. 12, 1930
  - Mercury (New Bedford, Mass.): The First Reader, by Harry Hansen-duplicate Of Nov. 12., Nov. 13, 1930
  - Leaf Chronicle (Clarksville, Tn.): "I'll Take My Stand.", Nov. 13, 1930
  - Virginian Pilot (Norfolk, Va.): The First Reader, by Harry Hansen-duplicate Of Nov. 12., Nov. 14, 1930
  - Publishers Weekly: citation of I'll Take My Stand., Nov. 15, 1930
  - Transcript (Boston, Mass.): citation of I"ll Take My Stand., Nov. 15, 1930
  - Sentinel (Orlando, Florida): "A Southern Book By Southerners", Nov. 15, 1930
  - Star (Kansas City, Mo.): "They Deplore Coming of Machinery in the South.", Nov. 15, 1930
  - The Chattanooga News: "The Young Confederates Take Their Stand/Dr. Hesseltine Reviews New Book by Southern Thinkers Who Would Carry the Trend Away from Industrialism and Back to Life of Contentment on the South's Beautiful Acres," reviewed by Dr. W. B. Hesseltine., Nov. 15, 1930
  - Enterprise (High Point, N. C.): "Agrarian Way of Living is Book Subject/ Southern Writers Define a Positive Philosophy As Opposed to the Present Day Industrialism.", Nov. 16, 1930
  - News Courier (Charleston, S. C.): "Book On South Is Out/ 12 Southerners Write of Agrarian Tradition.", Nov. 16, 1930
  - New York Times: citation of I'll Take My Stand., Nov. 16, 1930
  - Journal (Knoxville, Tn.): "Southern Agrarians Protest Industrialism's Encroachment," review of I'll Take My Stand by James I. Finney., Nov. 16, 1930
  - Post Dispatch (St. Louis, Missouri): Of Making Many Books, "Antaean Voices," review of I'll Take My Stand., Nov. 17, 1930
  - Register (Des Moines, Iowa): "Back to the South.", Nov. 19, 1930
  - Publishers Weekly: citation of I'll Take My Stand.", Nov. 22, 1930
  - Tribune (Jackson, Mich.): "In Dixie Land.", Nov. 22, 1930
  - Independent (St. Petersburg, Fla.): "Notes" on I'll Take My Stand., Nov. 22, 1930
  - Register (Mobile, Ala.): "In Dixie Land," duplicate of Nov. 22., Nov. 23, 1930
  - Advertiser (Montgomery, Ala.): "A Militant Indictment of ‘Progress.'" Review of I'll Take My Stand by W.J. M., Jr., Nov. 23, 1930
  - Folder
  - News (Greensboro, N. C.): The First Reader, duplicate of Nov. 12., Nov. 25, 1930
  - Nashville Tennessean: I Reckon So, by T. H. Alexander, comment on I'll Take My Stand., Nov. 25, 1930
  - Gazette (Gastonia, N. C.): comment on I'll Take My Stand., Nov. 26, 1930
  - Macon Telegraph: In My Opinion, by Coleman Hill, comment on I'll Take My Stand., Nov. 27, 1930
  - Commercial Appeal (Memphis, Tn.): I Reckon So, by T. H. Alexander, Duplicate of Nov. 25., Nov. 27, 1930
  - Press (Savannah, Ga.): The Literary Lantern, " Is the Industrialism of the South Inevitable?" review of I'll Take My Stand by Paul Green and Elizabeth Lay Green., Nov. 29, 1930
  - Evening Sun (Baltimore, Md.): "Symposium on the Industrial Problem of the New South," review of I'll Take My Stand and of The Industrial Revolution in the South, latter by Broadus Mitchell and George Sinclair Mitchell., Nov. 29, 1930
  - Star (Wilmington, N. C.): "In Dixie Land," duplicate of Nov. 22, Nov. 30, 1930
  - Macon Telegraph: In My Opinion, by Coleman Hill, comment on I'll Take My Stand., duplicate Nov. 27., Nov. 30, 1930